<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Website on Josh Padnick</title>
    <link>https://JoshPadnick.com/categories/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Website on Josh Padnick</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://JoshPadnick.com/categories/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Launched My New Website!</title>
      <link>https://JoshPadnick.com/2019/01/13/i-launched-my-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JoshPadnick.com/2019/01/13/i-launched-my-new-website/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m so happy to announce that I finally launched my new website, the very one you&amp;rsquo;re reading right now. I really enjoy writing for its own sake, but my old Wordpress blog eventually got some configuration issues and rather than fix it, I just wanted to move to a staticly generated site.
I chose Hugo, a Go-based static site generator and it was a pleasure to work with. At every step, Hugo was an accelerator, never a blocker. Hugo is well-documented, relatively easy to learn, supports all the major features I needed (pagination, categories/tags, partial templates, CSS compilation and magnification, lots of template functions, custom URLs, markdown-based authorship), and of course you have the full power of Go at your finger tips.
I did the bulk of the work over my holiday vacation. I allocated two days, and it wound up taking 4 days total. Yep, even this humble blog followed the typical software development pattern of things taking about twice as long as you originally expected. As a result, the design is pretty limited. If you have any design suggestions, I&amp;rsquo;d appreciate your sharing them. In the near future, I hope to also add a commenting feature back in.
I&amp;rsquo;d also like to thank Ibtehaj Raza who helped me migrate a bunch of the content from my old blog to the new one.
I haven&amp;rsquo;t written anything new on this blog in nearly 1.5 years! It will be fun to start writing thoughts again as I encounter them. Between growing Gruntwork, growing my kids, and life in general, I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>